UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Records 6000/026
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Jones, Day Employment Cases King's Congressional Testimony, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Legal Correspondence re: Objections to '97 Election, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- FLD 97: Contempt Petition 8-6-97, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Fieldcrest: Remedies & Access, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- NLRB Decision Media 9/5/95, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- FLD NLRB Articles 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Fieldcrest: 4th Circuit Decision, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- NLRB Clarification Case, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- FLD: Contempt Case, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- FLD: 1995 NLRB Decision (Box 8, Folder 20)
- FTX99 Church Materials, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- PTX '98 Church Outreach, 1982-1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- FLD Church Outreach 8/97, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- FLD: Community Campaign '97, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- FLD Community: Church Lit. '97, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- FLD/PTX: Church Nat'ls '97-'99, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- PTX UNITE Success Stories, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Community Campaign, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- In-Plant Meetings, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- PTX: 1999 Kick-off News Event 6/9/99 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- PTX: Leshner Benefits, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- PTX: Video #1, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Podesto.com, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Plant Saves, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Shut down Agreements Cone/Leshner, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Video #3 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Video Two, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Special Binder Product, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Peter D. Hart Research Associates, Inc., 1999 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Information for Organizers, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- PTX: Message, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- PTX: Probes, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Plants Saved by UNITE 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Hathaway Plant Save, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- PTX: WAC Victory Articles, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Plant Save Clips, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- FLD UNITE Plant Save Articles, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- PTX: UNITE Pension Stories (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Background - Closings, Rai Strikes, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- PTX '97 UNITE Strike Statistics, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- UNITE Bargaining & Organizing, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Modernization, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Gathering Plant Save Articles for Special Binder Product, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- FLD Health Insurance: History, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- PTX Final Tally, Vote Grant '99, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Clippings, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Cannon Historical Article Packet, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Press after Victory (Nov. '99), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- PTX Sets of Reco Articles, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- PTX Press on 1st Contract Rat., Kupl, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Newspapers, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- PTX: Ratification Clips, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Press after Victory until Oct'99, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- PTX Original Press '99 Campaign, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- PTX Paste-Ups: Reco Articles, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- PTX Recco, Media 11/99, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Maps & Restaurants, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- FLD Blanket Division - Articles History, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- NC Courts of Appeals (Raleigh) ASBESTOS, 1989-1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Fingerhut - Current, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Fieldcrest: Asbestos, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Pillowtex: Lobbying, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Asbestos - Court Research (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Workers Comp, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Asb: OSHA Studies, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- OSHA, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Notes, 1987-1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- For Educational Use Only, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- FLD: NC Dehnr - Asbestos, Etc. Printout, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- OSHA Swink - 16, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- OSHA - N.C.F., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Data Times. James M. Fitzgibbons, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Data Times - Robert E. Dellinger, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Data Times - Fred Bittle, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Data Times Jon C. Hurned, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- William H. Heitman, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Noah T. Herndon, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- S. Roger Horchow - Data Times, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- James A. Joyce, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Chris Kametches, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Data Times - C.J. Kjorlien, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Gloria Lang, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Data Times - John M. Nevin, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Clifford D. Paulsen, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Clifford D. Paulsen, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Richard E. Reece, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Joanne C. Rumbley, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Thomas R. Staab, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Alexandra Stoddard, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Data Times - D. Keith Wayne, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Nancy Webster, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- M. Kenneth Doss, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Data times - William E. Ford, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Article Search - James River 90-95, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Drcyfus '97, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- FLD: CEO Letters, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- FLD97: Reece - Signed Documents, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- FLD's letter to workers re: election objections Aug. 28/97, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- FLD: NLRB election history, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- James Fitzgibbons, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- PTX Podesta. Com - Corporate Background, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- PTX Podesta. Com - Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Podesta - PTX, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Podesta - CA Poultry Industry Found., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Podesta - Nat'l Environmental Strategies, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Podesta - Prison Health Services, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- National Council of Agricultural Podesta Employers, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Digital Equipment Corp. - Podesta, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Podesta - Air Implementation Reform Coalition, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Podesta - Nat'l Food Processors Assoc., 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Podesta - American Crop Protection Assoc., 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Podesta - Textron, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Podesta - Air Quality Standards Coalition, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Podesta - Air Products + Chemical Inc., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Podesta - Motion Picture Assoc. of America, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Podesta - Pharmaceutical Research + Manufacturers of America, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Podesta - Seagrams MCA Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Podesta - Numark Assoc, Inc., 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Podesta - American Insurance Assoc., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Podesta - Dow Agro Sciences LLC, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Podesta - Novartis, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Podesta - Horsehead Industries Inc., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Podesta - Genentech, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Podesta - CA. Healthcare Institute, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Podesta Children's Defense Fund Action Council, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Podesta Americans United to save the Arts + Humanities, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Podesta - CBS, Inc., 1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Podesta - Competitive Consumer Lending Coalition, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Podesta - Creative Community Task Force for Cancer Research, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Podesta - Friends of Cancer Research, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Podesta - Friends of Cancer Research, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Podesta Julien J. Studley, Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Podesta Kaplan Educational Centers, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Lockhead Martin Corp. Podesta, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Podesta MCI Communications Corp., 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Podesta Newspaper Assoc. of America, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Recording Industry Assoc. of America Podesta, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Podesta - Nat'l Assoc. of Broadcasters, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Podesta - San Mateo County, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- UNITE - UN97-O6R -- "Come Together" (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Cannon Anti- Rally - Aug. 3, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- UNITE -- "Justice" (Box 13, Folder 1)